(Howard:)Wrong pitcher.
(Bernadette:)I told you I'm not good with kids.
(Howard:)Yes, you did.
(Howard:)I think my crotch is starting to curdle.
(Bernadette:)The thing is,
my mother worked full-time.
(Bernadette:)I had to take care of
my brothers and sisters.
- Yeah, so?
- Uh, it was horrible.
(Bernadette:)With their snotty noses
and their poopy diapers...
(Bernadette:)...and their little shrieky voices,
always complaining.
"l don't wanna get dressed."
"Joey keeps spitting in my mouth."
"This isn't the way Mom
makes waffles."
(Bernadette:)Well, okay, put your hand in here.
Let's see how you like this waffle.
(Howard:)All right, settle down.
Red light. Red light.
Red light. Okay, we're fine.
(Bernadette:)I'm sorry. I know it makes me
sound like a bad person...
(Bernadette:)- ...but I just don't like children.
- Yeah, no, we all got that.